A Finding Aid to the Architectural League of New York Records, 1880s-1974, bulk 1927-1968, in the Archives of American Art AAA.archleag
Archives of American Art
- Exhibitions, 1887-1972, bulk 1930s-1960s; Series 5; 21.85 Linear feet Boxes 62-83, 111; OVs 117-119
  - Exhibition Committee, 1919-1967; 5.1
    - Birch Burdette Long, Minor L. Bishop-Exhibition Committee Chairman, 1963-1966; (2 folders) (Box 62, Folder 36-37)
    - Blueprints and Architectural Drawings, Etc., 1927-1959; (Oversized materials housed in OV 117) (Box 62, Folder 38)
    - Chairman, Baker, Douglas H., 1956-1957 (Box 62, Folder 39)
    - Chairman (Box 63)
      - Bishop, Minor L., 1962-1966; (2 folders) (Box 63, Folder 1-2)
      - Cheek, Leslie, Jr., 1947-1948; (3 folders) (Box 63, Folder 3-5)
      - Fernandez, Jose, 1954-1956 (Box 63, Folder 6)
      - Kagan, Vladimir, (1958-1959) (Box 63, Folder 7)
      - Ketchum, Morris, 1944-1947; (2 folders) (Box 63, Folder 8-9)
      - Price, Chester B., 1942-1944; (2 folders) (Box 63, Folder 10-11)
      - Reinhard, L. Andrew, 1939 (Box 63, Folder 12)
      - Schwartzman, Daniel [Chairman?], 1948-1950 (Box 63, Folder 13)
    - Chairman of Clubhouse, Lorimer Rich, 1942-1943 (Box 63, Folder 14)
    - City Planning Exhibition, 1951 (Box 63, Folder 15)
    - Columbian Exhibition, 1951 (Box 63, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence, 1950-1951 (Box 63, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence (Box 63)
      - Bien, Robert L., 1957-1958 (Box 63, Folder 18)
      - Complaints, 1955-1956 (Box 63, Folder 19)
      - Fuller, Clement re: Exhibit - Octych, 1958 (Box 63, Folder 20)
      - III Biennial Hispano Americana, 1955 (Box 63, Folder 21)
      - Magruder, Charles, 1947 (Box 63, Folder 22)
    - Current Work 1940-1941, Art Calendar (Requests from Magazines, Press, etc. for Schedules of Exhibitions) (Box 63, Folder 23)
    - The Early Californians Exhibition, 1951 (Box 63, Folder 24)
    - "Environment V" Press Release, 1967 (Box 63, Folder 25)
    - Exhibition Schedules, 1945-1946, 1953-1954; (2 folders) (Box 63, Folder 26-27)
    - Exhibitors Advisory Council, Inc., 1954 (Box 63, Folder 28)
    - [Fall Exhibition] (June 21, 1939), 1939-1940 (Box 63, Folder 29)
    - Haskell, Douglas, 1945 (Box 63, Folder 30)
    - Material for Arranging Exhibitions, 1960; (Oversized materials housed in OV 118) (Box 63, Folder 31)
    - Minutes, 1919-1924, 1953-1963; (4 folders) (Box 63, Folder 32-35)
    - Miscellaneous, 1940, 1952-1956; (3 folders) (Box 63, Folder 36-38)
    - Pratt Institute Department of Illustration, 1952-1955 (Box 63, Folder 39)
    - Requests re: Exhibitions and How They Are Handled, 1956-1959 (Box 63, Folder 40)
    - Unfinished Business and Miscellaneous, 1946 (Box 63, Folder 41)
    - Blueprints and Architectural Drawings, Etc., 1927-1959; (Oversized materials from Box 62, Folder 38) (Box OV 117)
    - Material for Arranging Exhibitions, Architectural Drawings, 1960; (Oversized materials from Box 63, Folder 31) (Box OV 118)
  - Exhibitions (Chronological), 1924-1971; 5.2
    This series provides a chronological history of exhibitions held at the League, both sponsored by the League or held by others. Materials include correspondence, blueprints, administrative records, notices and memos, and other records created in organizing exhibitions. Similar materials can be found in Functions and Events series and the Current Work subseries of the Committee Records series.
    Folders are arranged chronologically by year and exhibition date; exhibitions in which the exact date is unknown are filed at the beginning of the year in which the exhibition was most likely held.
    - "Architectural and Allied Arts Exposition,", 1924-1929 (Box 63, Folder 42)
    - National Exposition of Architecture, Decorative and Industrial Arts (Oct. 10-19, 1935) (Box 63, Folder 43)
    - A.I.D. Exhibition, Blueprint (Feb. 1936), (Oversized material housed in OV 118) (Box 63, Folder 44)
    - Karl Edelmann Exhibit, 1939 (Box 63, Folder 45)
    - 1940 Exhibitions (Box 63)
      - "The Boars," Carl Milles, re: Collection Books, 1940-1941 (Box 63, Folder 46)
      - Mrs. I.B. Markell Exhibition (List of Exhibits and Prices), circa 1940-1941 (Box 63, Folder 47)
      - Current Work 1939-1940, "Versus" (March 1940) (Box 63, Folder 48)
    - 1940 Exhibitions (Box 64)
      - "Versus" (Mar. 1940) (Box 64, Folder 1)
      - Current Work 1939-1940, Cornell University Exhibition (Apr. 29 - May 11, 1940) (Box 64, Folder 2)
      - Panel Exhibits Cocktail Party (Oct. 31, 1940) (Box 64, Folder 3)
      - Panel Exhibits Cocktail Party (Nov. 29, 1940) (Box 64, Folder 4)
      - Panel Exhibits Cocktail Party (Dec. 1940) (Box 64, Folder 5)
    - 1941 Exhibitions (Box 64)
      - Current Work 1940-1941, Panel Exhibits (Photographs Taken) (Box 64, Folder 6)
      - Panel Exhibits, Mr. Lorimer Rich, 1941 (Box 64, Folder 7)
      - Current Work 1941-1942, Panel Exhibits Cocktail Parties (Box 64, Folder 8)
      - Panel Exhibits Cocktail Party (Jan. 1941) (Box 64, Folder 9)
      - Current Work 1940-1941, "The Alumni of McKim, Mead and White" (Feb. 1941) (Box 64, Folder 10)
      - Panel Exhibits Cocktail Party (Feb. 1941) (Box 64, Folder 11)
      - Panel Exhibits Cocktail Party (Mar. 1941) (Box 64, Folder 12)
      - "40 Under 40" (Mar. 6-28, 1941), 1940-1941; (8 folders) (Box 64, Folder 13-20)
      - Current Work 1940-1941, "Forty Architects Under 40" Dinner and Exhibition (Mar. 6-28, 1941, inclusive) (Box 64, Folder 21)
      - Current Work 1940-1941, "Architecture Around San Francisco Bay" Exhibition, Miscellaneous Correspondence (Mar. 29 - Apr. 18, 1941), (Oversized materials housed in OV 118) (Box 64, Folder 22)
      - Panel Exhibits Cocktail Party (Apr. 1941) (Box 64, Folder 23)
      - Current Work 1940-1941, Sculpture Show Sponsored by the League (Apr. 22 - May 9, 1941), (7 folders) (Box 64, Folder 24-30)
      - Current Work 1941-1942, Panel Exhibits (Nov. 1941) (Box 64, Folder 31)
    - 1942 Exhibitions (Box 64)
      - Current Work 1941-1942, Panel Exhibitors (Corres. re: Pub. Fee) (Box 64, Folder 32)
      - O. Rundel Gilbert Exhibit, 1942-1944 (Box 64, Folder 33)
      - Panel Exhibits Cocktail Party (Jan. 1942), 1941-1942 (Box 64, Folder 34)
      - Panel Exhibits Cocktail Party (Feb. 1942) (Box 64, Folder 35)
      - Current Work 1941-1942, Panel Exhibits (Apr. 1942) (Box 64, Folder 36)
    - 1943 Exhibitions (Box 64)
      - "New Buildings for 194X" Exhibit, Mr. Price, 1943 (Box 64, Folder 37)
      - Navy Artists Exhibit, Mr. Price (July 12-16, 1943), 1943-1944 (Box 64, Folder 38)
    - 1944 Exhibitions (Box 64)
      - New Members Show, Blueprints, 1944; (Oversized material housed in OV 118) (Box 64, Folder 39)
      - New Members Signature Show, 1944 (Box 64, Folder 40)
      - "Progress of Prefabrication" (Mar. 9-28, 1944), 1943-1944; (3 folders) (Box 64, Folder 41-43)
    - 1944 Exhibitions (Box 65)
      - Renderings Exhibition (Apr. 10 - May 18, 1944) (Box 65, Folder 1)
    - 1945 Exhibitions (Box 65)
      - Mexican Exhibition, 1945 (Box 65, Folder 2)
      - "Architecture and the Arts Contribution to the War," Douglas Haskell (Oct. 1945) (Box 65, Folder 3)
    - 1946 Exhibitions (Box 65)
      - Claire Falkenstein Exhibit, 1946-1947 (Box 65, Folder 4)
      - Kawneer Company Exhibition, 1946-1947 (Box 65, Folder 5)
      - Roger Sturtevant Exhibit (Jan. 4-31, 1946), 1946-1948 (Box 65, Folder 6)
      - Walter Kilham, Jr. Exhibition (Feb. 26 - Mar. 16, 1946) (Box 65, Folder 7)
      - "Arts on the Newstand" Traveling Exhibition (May 1946), 1946-1947 (Box 65, Folder 8)
      - New Members Work and Summer Sketches Exhibition (Oct. 3-19, 1946) (Box 65, Folder 9)
    - 1947 Exhibitions (Box 65)
      - Chen Chi Exhibit, 1947 (Box 65, Folder 10)
      - "Team Design," Mary Roche, Chairman, 1947-1948 (Box 65, Folder 11)
      - Roman N. Verhovskoy Exhibition, 1947-1948 (Box 65, Folder 12)
      - Guild of Book Workers Gallery Space, Mrs. Otto von Wassilko (Feb. 3-15, 1947), 1946-1947 (Box 65, Folder 13)
      - Progressive Architecture Exhibit (Mar. 22-23, 1947) (Box 65, Folder 14)
      - "Tomorrow's Buildings" (May 22 - Sept. 15, 1947) (Box 65, Folder 15)
      - Otto Faelton Exhibition (June 17-28, 1947) (Box 65, Folder 16)
      - Architectural School Exhibition, Charles Magruder, Chairman (Fall 1947) (Box 65, Folder 17)
      - Benno Movin-Hermes Swedish Exhibition (Sept. 16-26, 1947) (Box 65, Folder 18)
      - Polish Exhibit, "Warsaw Lives Again" (Oct. 1947) (Box 65, Folder 19)
      - "U.S. Training for Architects 1947," Charles Magruder (Nov. 6-29, 1947), 1947-1948 (Box 65, Folder 20)
      - "U.S. Training for Architects, 1947" Traveling Exhibition (Nov. 6-29, 1947), 1947-1950; (6 folders) (Box 65, Folder 21-26)
      - "Modern Sculpture for Architecture" (Dec. 11-22, 1947) (Box 65, Folder 27)
    - 1948 Exhibitions (Box 65)
      - Christmas Card Exhibition, 1948 (Box 65, Folder 28)
      - Kaiser Friedrich Collection Exhibition of Paintings, 1948 (Box 65, Folder 29)
      - Designs for Decorators Exhibition (Feb. 27 - Mar. 13, 1948) (Box 65, Folder 30)
      - Edward P. Chrystie Renderings Exhibition, Winner of B.B. Long Prize for 1947 (May 7-22, 1948) (Box 65, Folder 31)
      - Sculpture Exhibition, Lu Duble (May-June 1948) (Box 65, Folder 32)
      - Sculpture in Lobby, Lu Duble [May-June 1948?], 1948-1949 (Box 65, Folder 33)
      - New Members and Members Summer Work (Oct. 17-29, 1948) (Box 65, Folder 34)
      - "My Favorite Unexecuted Work" (Nov. 22 - Dec. 3, 1948) (Box 65, Folder 35)
    - 1949 Exhibitions (Box 65)
      - A and G Perret, Architects Exhibit, 1949 (Box 65, Folder 36)
      - Eidlitz, French, Fink and Markle Exhibition, 1949-1950 (Box 65, Folder 37)
      - Havana, Cuba Exhibitions, 1949 (Box 65, Folder 38)
      - Ketchum, Gina and Sharp Exhibition, 1949 (Box 65, Folder 39)
      - Mary Roche Exhibition, 1949-1951 (Box 65, Folder 40)
      - "Sweden Today," Lundberg, Hogar, Swedish News Agency, circa 1949 (Box 65, Folder 41)
      - Tice and Lynch, Inc., Brokers Exhibition, 1949-1950 (Box 65, Folder 42)
      - Traveling Exhibition, Skidmore, Owings and Merrill - Terrace Plaza Hotel, Distinguished, Etc., 1949- 1950 (Box 65, Folder 43)
      - J. Scott Williams Exhibit, 1949 (Box 65, Folder 44)
      - Exhibition of Scandinavian Architecture by Lars Marnus (May 16-20, 1949) (Box 65, Folder 45)
      - James McCutchen and Co. Exhibit (June 13-24, 1949 (Box 65, Folder 46)
      - Legation of Switzerland Exhibit, Mr. Eric Kessler, Counselor of Legation (Sept. 12-24, 1949) (Box 65, Folder 47)
      - Henry Hering Memorial Exhibition, Gallery C (Sept. 26 - Oct. 28, 1949) (Box 65, Folder 48)
      - New Members and Members Summer Work (Oct. 1949), 1949-1950 (Box 65, Folder 49)
      - New Members Work Exhibition (Oct. 10-22, 1949) (Box 65, Folder 50)
      - "New Skylines of Manhattan," Gallery C (Oct. 24 - Nov. 12, 1949) (Box 65, Folder 51)
      - Kahn and Jacobs Exhibition (Oct. 31 - Nov. 12, 1949) (Box 65, Folder 52)
    - 1950 Exhibitions (Box 65)
      - Beaux-Arts Institute of Design Exhibition, 1950 (Box 65, Folder 53)
      - Panamericano de Arquitectos Exhibit, 1950 (Box 65, Folder 54)
      - Traveling Exhibition, "A Decade of Architecture,", 1950 (Box 65, Folder 55)
      - Traveling Exhibition, "Architectural Education of the United States,", 1950 (Box 65, Folder 56)
      - Shreve, Lamb and Harper Exhibition (Jan. 16-28, 1950) (Box 65, Folder 57)
      - Art Directors Exhibition (Feb. 6-13, 1950), 1949-1950 (Box 65, Folder 58)
      - American Institute of Graphic Arts Exhibition (Feb. 6-25, 1950), 1949-1950 (Box 65, Folder 59)
      - O'Connor and Kilham Exhibition (Feb. 27 - Mar. 11, Extended to Mar. 18, 1950), 1949-1950 (Box 65, Folder 60)
      - Edward Stone Exhibition (Mar. 7-18, Extended to Mar. 25, 1950) (Box 65, Folder 61)
      - Mrs. Clara Fargo Thomas Exhibition (Mar. 20-25, 1950) (Box 65, Folder 62)
      - James Seeman Exhibit (Apr. 3-8, 1950), 1949-1950 (Box 65, Folder 63)
      - LeBrun Traveling Scholarship Work Exhibition (Apr. 10-15, 1950) (Box 65, Folder 64)
      - Art Directors Exhibition (Apr. 17-29, 1950) (Box 65, Folder 65)
      - National Sculpture Society Exhibition, Bas Relief (May 2-11, 1950) (Box 65, Folder 66)
      - Traveling Exhibition, Growth on Projects in Architects Office, O'Connor and Kilham (June 1950) (Box 65, Folder 67)
      - "Architect With a Camera Visits South America" Exhibition and Luncheon (Aug. 28 - Sept. 15, 1950) (Box 65, Folder 68)
    - 1950 Exhibitions (Box 66)
      - Members Summer Exhibition, Gallery "A" (Sept. 18-30, 1950) (Box 66, Folder 1)
      - Richards Morgenthau Company Exhibition, Gallery "A" (Oct. 9-14, 1950) (Box 66, Folder 2)
      - Gwen Lux Exhibition (Sculptured Panels and Theatrical Masks), Dining Room (Oct. 9-30, 1950) (Box 66, Folder 3)
      - "Hand Painted Under Glazed Tiles," Pine Room (Oct. 16-28, 1950) (Box 66, Folder 4)
      - "Competition for Garden City Village Hall," Pine Room (Oct. 30 - Nov. 4, 1950) (Box 66, Folder 5)
      - Avant Garde (Kootz Gallery) Exhibition, Gallery "A" (Oct. 30 - Nov. 11, 1950) (Box 66, Folder 6)
      - Columbia University (Traveling Exhibition), Pine Room (Nov. 6-10, 1950 (Box 66, Folder 7)
      - Popular Photographers Exhibition, Gallery "A" (Nov. 6-18, 1950) (Box 66, Folder 8)
      - Advertising Agencies Service Co. Exhibition, Pine Room (Nov. 13-25, 1950) (Box 66, Folder 9)
      - Moss Rose Manufacturing Co. (Auerbach Assoc.) Exhibition, Gallery "A" (Nov. 13-20, 1950) (Box 66, Folder 10)
      - Institute of International Education Exhibition, Dining Room (Dec. 5-15, 1950), 1950- 1951 (Box 66, Folder 11)
      - Art Directors Club Exhibition, Gallery "A" (Dec. 11-16, 1950) (Box 66, Folder 12)
    - 1951 Exhibitions (Box 66)
      - Josef Hoffmann Exhibition, 1951 (Box 66, Folder 13)
      - Society of Architectural Historians, 1951 (Box 66, Folder 14)
      - G. Teilman Exhibition and Party, 1951 (Box 66, Folder 15)
      - American Institute of Graphic Arts Exhibition (Jan. 14 - Feb. 2, 1951) (Box 66, Folder 16)
      - Lithographers National Association Exhibition, Gallery "A" (Jan. 15-20, 1951), 1950 (Box 66, Folder 17)
      - Sheila Burlingame Exhibition, Pine Room (Jan. 15-27, 1951) (Box 66, Folder 18)
      - Lithographers National Association Exhibition, Gallery "A" (Feb. 19 - Mar. 3, 1951) (Box 66, Folder 19)
      - Art Directors Club Exhibition, Pine Room (Feb. 26 - Mar. 3, 1951) (Box 66, Folder 20)
      - Pratt Institute Exhibition, Pine Room (Mar. 19-31, 1951) (Box 66, Folder 21)
      - Pratt Institute Exhibition, Mr. Ajootian, Pine Room (Apr. 2-7 or 23-28, 1951) (Box 66, Folder 22)
      - Fitchburg Youth Library Exhibition (Apr. 30 - May 20, 1951) (Box 66, Folder 23)
      - Pratt Institute Department of Interior Design Exhibition (May 1951) (Box 66, Folder 24)
      - National Sculpture Society Exhibition (May 4-19, 1951), 1951-1952 (Box 66, Folder 25)
      - Architectural Photographers Association Exhibition (May 21 - June 2, 1951) (Box 66, Folder 26)
      - Techniques and Materials Exhibition (June 18-30, 1951) (Box 66, Folder 27)
      - "Graphic Art in Sweden Today," American-Swedish News Exchange (July 2-28, 1951) (Box 66, Folder 28)
      - Long-Avery Exhibition (Aug. 6 - Sept. 14, 1951) (Box 66, Folder 29)
      - "My Kitchen Contest" (Aug. 23-24, 1951) (Box 66, Folder 30)
      - Ontario Association of Architects Exhibition (Sept. 1951) (Box 66, Folder 31)
      - Members' Summer Show (Sept. 17-29, 1951), 1950-1951 (Box 66, Folder 32)
      - Engineers' Exhibit (Oct. 2-19, 1951) (Box 66, Folder 33)
      - Producers' Council Exhibition (Oct. 15-20, 1951) (Box 66, Folder 34)
      - American Artists Professional League Exhibition (Oct. 29 - Nov. 17, 1951) (Box 66, Folder 35)
      - American Artists Professional League Exhibition, Gallery "A" (Nov. 1-14, 1951) (Box 66, Folder 36)
      - David E. Squiers Exhibition (Nov. 12-17, 1951 - Cancelled) (Box 66, Folder 37)
      - Lumen Winter Exhibition (Nov. 13-17, 1951) (Box 66, Folder 38)
      - Screen Process and Display Association of New York Exhibition (Dec. 2-8, 1951), 1951-1952 (Box 66, Folder 39)
      - Beatrice West Exhibition (Dec. 10-15, 1951) (Box 66, Folder 40)
      - Art Directors Club Exhibition (Dec. 17-21, 1951) (Box 66, Folder 41)
    - 1952 Exhibitions (Box 66)
      - Hugh Ferriss Exhibition, 1952-1953 (Box 66, Folder 42)
      - Gropius Exhibit, 1952 (Box 66, Folder 43)
      - University of Illinois Exhibition, 1952-1953 (Box 66, Folder 44)
      - Zurich Exhibition, 1952 (Box 66, Folder 45)
      - Advertising Typographers Association of America Exhibition (Jan. 14-19, 1952) (Box 66, Folder 46)
      - State Board Examination Architectural Drawings Exhibition, Pine Room (Feb. 11-15, 1952) (Box 66, Folder 47)
      - "The Traveling Exhibition of Architectural Drawings," Dean Leopold Arnaud, Pine Room (Feb. 11-15, 1952) (Box 66, Folder 48)
      - C.W. Stockwell and Co. Exhibition, Virginia Hamill (Feb. 11-16, 1952), 1951-1952 (Box 66, Folder 49)
      - Art Directors Club Exhibition (Feb. 18 - Mar. 1, 1952), circa 1952 (Box 66, Folder 50)
      - Art Career School Exhibition (Mar. 3-8, 1952), 1951-1952 (Box 66, Folder 51)
      - Mauno Oittinen Exhibition (Mar. 3-8, 1952), 1951-1952 (Box 66, Folder 52)
      - Harold L. Walter Exhibition (Mar. 10-15, 1952) (Box 66, Folder 53)
      - Kelly and Gruzen Exhibition (Mar. 17-24, 1952) (Box 66, Folder 54)
      - Municipal Art Society Exhibition (Apr. 14-18, 1952) (Box 66, Folder 55)
      - Pratt Institute Exhibition, Mr. Longyear (Apr. 14-19, 1952) (Box 66, Folder 56)
      - Pratt Institute Department of Illustration Exhibition (Apr. 28 - May 2, 1952), 1951 (Box 66, Folder 57)
      - National Sculpture Society Exhibit (May 9-23, 1952) (Box 66, Folder 58)
      - Veteran Motor Car Club of America Exhibit (May 12-16, 1952) (Box 66, Folder 59)
      - Yalesburg Exhibit, Richardson Wood (May 26 - June 2, 1952) (Box 66, Folder 60)
      - Members' Summer Exhibition (July 23 - Sept. 5, 1952) (Box 66, Folder 61)
      - "Unexecuted Work" Exhibition and Party (Aug. 18 - Sept. 5, 1952) (Box 66, Folder 62)
      - Members Summer Work Exhibition (Sept. 25 - Oct. 10, 1952) and Cocktail Party (Sept. 24, 1952) (Box 66, Folder 63)
      - Producers' Council Exhibition (Oct. 20-24, 1952) (Box 66, Folder 64)
      - Virginia World War Exhibition (Nov. 1952) (Box 66, Folder 65)
      - David E. Squiers Exhibit, Pine Room (Nov. 24-28, 1952) (Box 66, Folder 66)
      - Frank Hoctor and James Herbert Exhibit (Dec. 1-20, 1952), 1952-1953 (Box 66, Folder 67)
      - New York State Architectural Examination Drawings Exhibition (Dec. 23, 1952 - Jan. 2, 1953) (Box 66, Folder 68)
    - 1953 Exhibitions (Box 66)
      - American Academy in Rome Exhibition, 1953-1954 (Box 66, Folder 69)
      - Blow Company Exhibition, 1953-1954 (Box 66, Folder 70)
      - Caribbean Architecture, 1953 (Box 66, Folder 71)
      - English Architecture, 1953 (Box 66, Folder 72)
      - Mrs. Ruth M. Kilby Exhibition, 1953-1954 (Box 66, Folder 73)
      - "Lettering Art in Modern Use," Raymond A. Ballinger (Jan. 25-31, 1953), 1952-1953 (Box 66, Folder 74)
      - Art Directors Exhibition (Mar. 2-7, 1953) (Box 66, Folder 75)
      - American Society of Landscape Architects Exhibition (Apr. 1953), 1953, 1955 (Box 66, Folder 76)
      - Lithographers National Association Exhibition (Apr. 1953), 1952-1953 (Box 66, Folder 77)
      - "When Work is Done," Leisure Time Activities of Trade Unionists (Apr. 23 - May 6, 1953) (Box 66, Folder 78)
      - Members Show (June 30, 1953) (Box 66, Folder 79)
      - Swiss Architecture (Sept. 1-20, 1953) (Box 66, Folder 80)
      - Members' Summer Show, T. Kilham, Chairman (Sept. 22 - Oct. 8, 1953) (Box 66, Folder 81)
      - Lighting Forum (Oct. 1953) (Box 66, Folder 82)
      - "New Work in Stained Glass" (Oct. 15 - Nov. 15, 1953) (Box 66, Folder 83)
      - "The Skyscraper" (Oct. 27 - Nov. 10, 1953) (Box 66, Folder 84)
      - Producers' Council Table-top Exhibition (Nov. 1953) (Box 66, Folder 85)
      - "Purcell and Elmslie" (Walker Art Center) (Nov. 1953) (Box 66, Folder 86)
      - "Public Housing Past, Present, Future" (Nov. 17-27, 1953) (Box 66, Folder 87)
      - Art Directors Exhibition (Dec. 14-19, 1953) (Box 66, Folder 88)
    - 1954 Exhibitions (Box 66)
      - American Institute of Steel Construction Exhibition, 1954 (Box 66, Folder 89)
      - Belgium Exhibit, J.R. Kingsley, 1954 (Box 66, Folder 90)
      - Members Informal Show, 1954 (Box 66, Folder 91)
      - Travel Posters Exhibition, 1954 (Box 66, Folder 92)
      - "Poems in Paint," W.B. Sherman (Mar. 31 - Apr. 12, 1954), 1953-1954 (Box 66, Folder 93)
      - "Architectural Schoolwork in the United States" (Apr. 20 - May 7, 1954), 1953-1955; (3 folders) (Box 66, Folder 94-96)
      - A.I.A. Lebrun Scholarship Competition Exhibition (May 17-21, 1954) (Box 66, Folder 97)
      - Columbia University School of Architecture Exhibition (May 24-29, 1954, Cancelled) (Box 66, Folder 98)
      - "Building Your Home, 1954" (May 27 - June 6, 1954), (3 folders) (Box 66, Folder 99-101)
    - 1954 Exhibitions (Box 67)
      - "Building Your Home, 1954" (May 27 - June 6, 1954), (5 folders) (Box 67, Folder 1-5)
      - Belgian Government Exhibition (Weeks of Sept. 13, 20, 27), 1954 (Box 67, Folder 6)
      - Borgenicht Gallery (Rugs by Contemporary Artists) - Date to be Fixed: Oct.-Nov., Pine Room - 2 Weeks, 1954 (Box 67, Folder 7)
      - Cuban Exhibition (Oct. 5-18, 1954) (Box 67, Folder 8)
      - Pietro Lazzari Exhibition, Agent-Dell Publishing Company (Oct. 5-19, 1954) (Box 67, Folder 9)
      - Gerald V. Davis Exhibition (Oct. 19 - Nov. 1, 1954) (Box 67, Folder 10)
      - Charles Cooper, Inc., Advertising Art (Oct. 26-30, 1954) (Box 67, Folder 11)
      - "Bridges Are Beautiful," American Federation of Arts (Nov. 2-22, 1954), 1953-1954 (Box 67, Folder 12)
      - Polish Architecture Exhibition (Nov. 3-9, 1954) (Box 67, Folder 13)
      - Jean Nison Exhibition, Pine Room (Nov. 18 - Dec. 3, 1954) (Box 67, Folder 14)
    - 1955 Exhibitions (Box 67)
      - Academy in Rome Exhibit, 1955 (Box 67, Folder 15)
      - American Institute of Architects Small House Exhibition, 1955 (Box 67, Folder 16)
      - Burma Exhibition, 1955 (Box 67, Folder 17)
      - Italian Exhibition, 1955 (Box 67, Folder 18)
      - Mexican Exhibition, 1955-1956 (Box 67, Folder 19)
      - "Light In Architecture" Lighting Exhibition (Jan. 17-29, 1955), 1954-1955; (2 folders) (Box 67, Folder 20-21)
      - Voorhees, Walker, Smith and Smith, Loyola Seminary Sculpture Exhibit (Feb. 10-24, [1955]), circa 1955 (Box 67, Folder 22)
      - Jack Lenor Larsen Exhibition of Textiles and Furniture (Apr. 18-23, 1955) (Box 67, Folder 23)
      - Ilonka Karasz Screens Exhibition (May 2-17, 1955), 1954 (Box 67, Folder 24)
      - Moore and Company Marble Exhibition (Sept. 11-30, 1955) (Box 67, Folder 25)
      - Murals Inc. Wall Coverings Exhibition, James Seeman (Oct. 1955) (Box 67, Folder 26)
      - Container Corporation of America Exhibit, Color Harmony Manual, Mr. Walter Granville (Oct. 3-14, 1955) (Box 67, Folder 27)
      - Mauretania Fabrics, Inc. Exhibition, Margit Pinter (Oct. 10-21, 1955) (Box 67, Folder 28)
      - Biow-Beirn-Toigo Exhibit (Oct. 13-19, 1955) (Box 67, Folder 29)
      - Charles Cooper, Inc. Exhibition - Advertising Art (Oct. 24-28, 1955) (Box 67, Folder 30)
      - Donelda Fazakas Exhibit and Cocktail Party (Oct. 24-29, 1955) (Box 67, Folder 31)
      - Photo Engravers Exhibit (Nov. 6-19, 1955) (Box 67, Folder 32)
      - Mrs. Joseph Judge Exhibition and Tea (Dec. 1955) (Box 67, Folder 33)
    - 1956 Exhibitions (Box 67)
      - Architectural Drawings Exhibited in London Embassy Competition, 1956 (Box 67, Folder 34)
      - "Architectural School Work in the United States," List of Exhibitors, 1956 (Box 67, Folder 35)